eldarya.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Eldarya

Privacy is fundamental to BEEMOOV. This “General Privacy Policy” applies to all visitors and users of [www.eldarya.com](http://www.eldarya.com/). You must agree to the Terms of Service before enjoying the benefits of a registered user.

Each MEMBER can share personal information on forums accessible by other MEMBERS. Here’s how it works: 

  * Any MEMBER can view Forum discussions, comments or any other private information that a MEMBER may post to the PLATFORM. 
  * We don’t share your private information with anyone (except for operating the Website). 
  * If you post any content on the Website, you are making it available publicly. Your submission of any content is subject to the right of BEEMOOV to remove inappropriate postings. 

BEEMOOV has instituted measures to protect the security and content of the forums. 

BEEMOOV regularly monitors its forums through a team of volunteers, a country manager and potentially others acting on behalf of BEEMOOV. BEEMOOV does not control the content of any messages before publication. Any delays in such post-publication review may result in potentially substantial distribution to an online audience before actual review. 

**You should avoid disclosing any personal information that you do not wish to make public to other MEMBERS.**

Welcome to the [www.eldarya.com](http://www.eldarya.com/) Website (the “Website”). We are happy that you have chosen to visit our Website and learn more about our company. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Website. We will not use or share your Personal Information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

In this Privacy Policy the term “eldarya.com” refers to our Website, the homepage of which is located at eldarya.com; the terms “us” or “we” or “our” refers to BEEMOOV, Inc. (“BEEMOOV”), the owner of eldarya.com, and the terms “you” or “user” refer to the user or viewer of eldarya.com. Other capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Service. 

When using BEEMOOV, there are general elements of our service that you should know. Access to our database is granted only to our technicians on a case-by-case basis to troubleshoot specific technical issues, or as may be required by law. For further details on using BEEMOOV, please refer to our Terms of Service Agreement, located here. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact: [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com) or send mail to Privacy, BEEMOOV SAS, 57 Boulevard Gaston Serpette, 44000 Nantes, France. 

BEEMOOV complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. BEEMOOV has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view the company’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

As we update and expand our Website, this Privacy Policy may change, so please check this web page for updates to our Privacy Policy. 

###  Collection of Information 

When you visit our Website we may collect information regarding your visit from your computer. Such information helps us to determine information about how you found our Website, the date that you visited our Website and search engines that may have led you to our Website. We collect this information in order to continually improve and enhance the functionality of [www.eldarya.com](http://www.eldarya.com/)

Generally, you may provide us with two types of information, User Content, which may include Personal Information, and Website Usage Information, both of which are discussed in greater detail below. 

####  Retention of Information 

Your Personal Information may be retained for the period of your ongoing use plus up to three years after you expressly terminate your membership or your account is dormant for a period of four months. The tracking cookies may be retained for the period of your ongoing use after such termination or dormancy. Such retention periods may be extended if mandated by law or otherwise required for the protection of our rights. 

####  Children under age 13 

**This website is not directed to children under the age of 13 years. If you are under the age of 13, you are not allowed to use this site. We recommend that, if you are under 13, you should be smart and not provide any information on your identity, physical location or online contact information unless you do so under your parent’s consent and supervision.**

### Personal Information You Choose to Provide

In order to make your visits to our Website as enjoyable as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information. Personal Information includes, for example, your email address, which you are asked to provide when registering with BEEMOOV. Below is a description of some of the ways that you may provide Personal Information to us, as well as further details on how we may use such Personal Information. 

####  1\. Sign-Up Information and Profile 

You provide us with Personal Information, such as your email address, when you register a Member account with the Website. You may also choose to add information to your profile. 

####  2\. Contact Us/Feedback 

If you email us at [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com), we may ask you for information such as your name and email address so we can respond to your questions and comments. If you choose to correspond with us via email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our response to you. In certain cases, and with your permission, we may post content from your emails to us on the BEEMOOV Website. 

####  3\. Questionnaires and Surveys 

We may occasionally ask users of our Website to complete online surveys and opinion polls about their activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us better serve you and improve the usefulness of BEEMOOV. In requesting your participation in these surveys we may ask you to provide your name and email address to us. 

####  4\. User Content 

Our Website offers its users the opportunity to share User Content – for instance, on your user profile, status, the forum and through private messages. If you choose to use these features, you should be aware that any Personal Information you submit through these features can be read, collected, or used by other viewers of these forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums. 

####  5\. Import Contacts 

We may utilize an “import contacts” feature to help you keep in touch with your contacts and other members. This may make it easier for you to invite people from your email address book to join you on our Website. If implemented, you can manually import a file from your email program or you can provide us with your email username and password and the BEEMOOV program will import your email contacts for you. 

If you import your contacts, we may ask you if you wish to invite or follow your colleagues from your same domain. If you indicate that you would like to follow them, we will send them an invitation from you (with a return address of [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com)) to activate a BEEMOOV account and join the same domain network as you. We may also send one reminder message after the original invitation if we do not hear back from them. People you invite to join the Website may opt out of receiving further emails from BEEMOOV as described in the Rights to Opt In/Opt Out section below. 

### Website Usage Information

####  1\. Cookies 

We may use “cookies” on or in connection with our Website to maintain information about you. A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. BEEMOOV employs the use of both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. 

When you visit our Website, our computer may ask your computer for permission to employ the use of a session or persistent cookie. Our Website will then send a cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits our Website to access the cookies it has already sent to you and not the cookies sent to you by other websites. 

Most web browsers can be adjusted to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, our Website or certain areas or features of our Website. 

We work with business partners who provide advertising, technology services and other that goods and services to make your visit more interesting. We permit such business partners to add cookies to your computer and track your use of their information or services. We require such business partners to respect our privacy policy. 

####  2\. IP Address and Clickstream Data 

Our servers automatically collect data about your Internet Protocol address when you visit us. When you request pages from our Website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another website or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Website; the website you visit after this Website; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral website; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with Personal Information. 

Any or all of these activities with regard to the above-described Website Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our third-party service providers. (See “Sharing Information with Third Parties” section below). 

### Rights to Opt In/Opt Out

Information. For example, if you are prompted to provide Personal Information on this Website or in connection with our communications to you, you may have the opportunity to elect whether you would like to receive such correspondence from us. You may opt out of BEEMOOV’s promotional e-mails by clicking on the opt-out or “unsubscribe” link within the email you receive. You can also make this request by sending an email to [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com), specifying whether: (i) you would like to opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from BEEMOOV in general, or just via e-mail, postal mail and/or by phone, and/or whether (ii) you would only like to opt out of certain of BEEMOOV’s e-newsletters or correspondence. 

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. 

###  Use and Disclosure of Personal Information 

We will use your Personal Information to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Website Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including (without limitation) any of our other websites and third parties. If you choose to import your address book contacts as part of BEEMOOV’s invitation process, we may store those names and emails and display them to other MEMBERS in a forum on the Website in order to customize the Service for you and to enable you and coworkers in your Network to generate subsequent invitations. We may send you notices (for example, in the form of emails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Rights to Opt In/Opt Out section above. 

In addition, we may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and emails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. BEEMOOV will not share, rent or sell your Personal Information to other parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

####  1\. Service Providers 

We may use third-party partners to help us operate and maintain our Website and deliver our products and services. We may also share your Personal Information and Website Usage Information with our service providers and other third parties (“Affiliated Parties”) that provide products or services for or through this Website or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, communications providers, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, credit card processing companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). 

Third-party service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the Personal Information and Website Usage Information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements, or otherwise subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

####  2\. Aggregate Statistics 

We may disclose non-personally identifiable aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and emails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports, which do not describe or identify any individual user. Information relating to aggregate statistics may be collected through the use of third-party cookies and other third party tracking devices. 

####  3\. Legally Compelled Disclosures 

We may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with a judicial or court order or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Website, the users of the Website, and/or our Affiliated Parties; or (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our Website, us, or third parties. 

####  4\. Business Transfer 

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this Website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will notify you as described in “Updates to our Privacy Policy” 

### Consent to Worldwide Transfer and Processing of Personal Data

By providing Personal Information to us through this Website, you agree that it may be used by us and our Affiliated Parties for the purposes described herein and you further understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, which may have different privacy laws from your country of residence and which may afford varying levels of protection for your Personal Information. Regardless of the laws in place in these countries, we will treat the privacy of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By providing your Personal Information to this Website, you consent to our transmission to, and processing of your information in, any jurisdiction, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

###  Your Access and Correction Rights 

You retain the right to decline to submit Personal Information through BEEMOOV, in which case BEEMOOV may not be able to provide certain services to you. However, if you choose to provide Personal Information to BEEMOOV, we will provide you with the ability to access, correct, update or delete the Personal Information you have provided to this Website by emailing [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com) We will respond to your request within 30 days. However, before we are able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies, we may ask you to verify your identity and provide other details to help us to respond to your request. 

###  Third-Party Websites 

When you are on this Website you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other websites, including other websites operated by BEEMOOV or by unaffiliated third parties. These websites may collect Personal Information about you, and because this Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, you should review the privacy policies of such other websites to see how they treat your Personal Information. 

###  Security 

BEEMOOV and our partners uses commercially reasonable and industry standard physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We also use Secure Sockets Layer (BEEMOOV’s business partners, who permit purchases undertaken by players, use SSL technology) encryption to transmit sensitive information. While BEEMOOV endeavors to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information provided to this Website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. 

If you contact us by email or a “contact” or similar feature on the Website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. An unaffiliated third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. 

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email. You consent to our use of email as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please email us at [support@beemoov.com](mailto:support@beemoov.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used. 

###  Updates to Our General Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the date shown below. This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will post a prominent notice on this Website to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the top of the statement when it was most recently updated. If you access this site after a change, the new Privacy Policy will apply. 

**BEEMOOV, SAS,** with stated capital of 200 000 euros, registered at the RCS of Nantes, France under the number B 492 377 908 - TVA FR82492377908, with headquarters located at 57 boulevard Gaston Serpette, 44000 Nantes, France. 

© 2013 BEEMOOV SAS. All rights reserved. 

Version Last Updated: June 28, 2016.
